findartinfo.com 2005-04-07

# Art appraisal. Search auction prices for free!

## We are firmly committed to protecting the personal data we receive from our customers and visitors. We will only ask for the minimum information required to run this site.

It is our firm policy not to sell or in any other way disclose any personal information to any third party, except under the following curcumstances: 

  1. In some instances, we may need to disclose personal information about you to partner companies to provide you with the best possible service – for example this might be our secure payment partners. However, such companies will be under an obligation to keep your personal information confidential.   
 
  2. We may disclose personal information as required by law, for example in response to a court order or a subpoena. 

We will only use your personal information to run this site. Any other use will require your prior consent.  
Apart from signatures and basic information on artists, we do not collect any personal information. Our customers and visitors also provide information about themselves to us.  
We primarily collect signatures and pictures of paintings or other artwork from public sources such as art catalogues and museums. We also obtain information from art dealers and from the artists themselves.

If you are an artist and would like to see what information we have on you, please email to [ adm@FindArtInfo.com](mailto:adm@FindArtInfo.com) and we will make sure that you will get access to all information about you. Any corrections/updates will be highly appreciated.
